Day 11.
Already entered a mark 10:09 days Cara.
Now I am in a very big doubt.
I don't know if I see it on the street again while I wait for the answers.
So far no one has called Feteria's bro.
And then I'm kind of worried if I'm going to be able to if they don't call.
Man I have to do something expensive.
You have to bother me to sell on the street.
I don't know I have a lot of bad bro.
I think maybe it's a little anxiety because nobody called.
I will now do this.
I'll buy the inputs there.
Haha
song
I need to think of something more creative.
You know I don't know if I think of anything else.
If I change it and go to 1 other area.
Ah,
there are so many possibilities in a short time.
It kills me because my head thinks a million things it also draws.
I don't have time to think about this series because it's frenetic.
I'm waiting.
Answer has no answer.
Sorry to blow this up with you.
I think I need to think old I'm not getting it.
Usually when I do this I call someone to be able to clear my mind a little
bit to listen to people who are suddenly more often in good tune in a.
And then things flow.
And there and there little sister how is that?
Everything's fine,
I'm fine and you tell me Cara I'm in a bind.
I got 1 free little show yesterday in some places but
I'm apprehensive because nobody is calling me.
How do you add value not only within social networks here
but Ali in the physical space of these people.
They will have much more than a Passenger to bring home a kiss.
Also with Júlia tamo with valeu.
Bye bye,
let's see what I'm going to do tomorrow,
okay.